CONNOR CLUSTER

Clu.Codes@gmail.com | (352) 497-6301 | 5111 SE 18th St. Ocala, FL. 34480

GitHub: https://github.com/Clu-Codes

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/connor-cluster/

Portfolio: https://clu-codes.github.io/Clu-Codes/

Summary

Full-Stack Web Developer with a unique background of skills that exemplifies an ability to learn diverse fields of studies. Distinguished linguistic and logical reason skills that address the totality of work as a developer. Multiple years of experience in tech as a digital marketer.

Skills

Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, MySQL, Sequelize, JavaScript, jQuery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Materialize, AJAX, Git, Google Analytics & Search Console, Jest.js, Benchmark.js, Inquirer.js

Projects

Something Special – Full-Stack Group Project

GitHub: https://github.com/Clu-Codes/something-special

Deployed Site: https://cmnw-something-special.herokuapp.com/login

- o Project Summary: A community marketplace for listing new & used event items.
- o Role: Coordinated tasks, established front-end styling, developed login & sign-up page, edit page (with preview feature), co-operated with team to test & debug.
- o Tools: Node.js, Express.js, MySQL/Sequelize, Handlebars.js, Bcrypt, Firebase, JavaScript, HTML, Bootstrap, CSS, Heroku, Git & GitHub.

Dungeon's End – Third-Party API Group Project

GitHub: https://github.com/Clu-Codes/dungeons-end/

Deployed Site: https://clu-codes.github.io/dungeons-end/

- o Project Summary: A web-based Dungeons & Dragons monster encounter.
- Role: Established stand-ups, devised logic for capturing player info, fetching monster images, establishing diminishing returns on player actions, and reporting combat information.
- o Tools: Materialize, HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Employee Tracker – An Employee Database CLI

GitHub: https://github.com/Clu-Codes/employee-tracker

Demo Video: https://drive.google.com/file/d/1s3k9rOBU0MyCrPXW8fEKiSFJMTxTLv6t/view

- App Summary: Node.is CLI that empowers users to easily manage business functions
- o Role: Sole Contributor
- o Tools: Node.js, MySQL, JavaScript, Inquirer.js

Education

University of Central Florida – Full Stack Coding Bootcamp

October 2020 - April 2021

University of Florida – Bachelor of Arts – BA, English

August 2014 - May 2016

- o Graduated Cum Laude with a 3.74 GPA.
- o Former chair member of UF Phi Alpha Delta International Pre-Legal Fraternity

College of Central Florida – Associates of Arts – AA, General Studies

August 2012 – May 2014

- o Inducted into the Phi Theta Kappa Honor Society Graduated with 4.10 GPA
- o Member of the Forensics (Speech & Debate) team

Work Experience

Office Manager/Court Maintenance, Fort King Tennis Center - Ocala, FL

2010-2014

- Developed communication skills to facilitate the needs of the business and customers
- o Recorded and organized data to accelerate access to membership profiles
- Created systems that increased productivity during maintenance hours

Tennis Professional, Fort King Tennis Center – Ocala, FL

2014-2017

- Instructed youth and young adults about proper mechanics and movements related to tennis
- Learned to construct information in a manner that's easily understandable and applicable
- o Cultivated Professional Relationships with Clients

PPC/Search Engine Optimization Analyst, Raney's, Inc. - Ocala, FL

2017-2018

- o Analyze, Construct, and Manage Data to develop marketing strategies, increase profitability, and maximize return on investment
- o Create, Deploy, and Facilitate SEO strategies to improve search engine rankings
- Develop and Manage Ad Campaigns to increase brand awareness and Lifetime Customer Value
- Collaborate with developers to ensure website adheres to SEO best practices

Marketing Coordinator, Raney's, Inc. - Ocala, FL

2018-Present

- Manage Marketing Department's day-to-day operations
- Develop and deploy marketing campaigns & strategies across multi-faceted digital marketing channels (Email, SMS, Facebook, Google)
- o Foster & maintain 3rd-party integrations & relationships to advance revenue growth

References available upon request.